Register of the Victor Gilinsky Papers, 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION, 1974-1984
  - Fuel cycle
    - Waste management
      - General. Relates predominantly to the development of a consistent federal waste management policy, with emphasis on the need for permanent high-level waste storage facilities
        - 1979 May 10-Sept. Includes hearing of the Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources (Henry M. Jackson, Chairman), May 10; information on the Waste Isolation Pilot Plant in New Mexico, Aug. 1; Hart/Simpson Committee hearing, Sept. 13 (Box 261., Folder 1-11)
        - 1979 Oct.-1980 Jan. House Committee on Science and Technology, Subcommittee on Energy Research and Production (Mike McCormack, Chairman; hereafter referred to as the McCormack Committee) hearing, Nov. 7 (Box 262., Folder 1-9)
        - 1980 Feb.-May. Hart/Simpson Committee hearing, Jan. 23; Glenn/Percy Committee hearing, Feb. 13; McCormack Committee hearing May 29; Udall hearings March 18 and May 12; DOE report, "Final Environmental Impact Statement: U.S. Spent Fuel Policy," Vols. 1-2), 1980 May (Box 263., Folder 1-8)
        - 1980 May-July 25. DOE report, Vols. 3-5; Nuclear Waste Management Forum report, June (Box 264., Folder 1-9)
        - 1980 July 25-Sept. Dingell Committee hearings, July 25; Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition and Forestry, Subcommittee on Rural Development hearing, Aug. 26 (Box 265., Folder 1-8)
        - 1980 Sept.-1981 March. Visit to Hanford, Washington, Oct. 7; "Report of the Working Group on the Proposed Rulemaking on the Storage and Disposal of Nuclear Wastes," Jan. 29 (Box 266., Folder 1-11)
        - 1981 March-Sept. Includes comments on NRC Waste Confidence proceedings by interested groups, March; and materials relating to the proposed National Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1981; Udall Committee hearings, June 23, 25 and July 9 (Box 267., Folder 1-9)
        - 1981 Sept.-Dec. 11 Includes a draft report by the Office of Technology Assessment, ca. Dec. (Box 268., Folder 1-9)
        - 1981 Dec. 21-1982 Jan. 8. Includes extensive briefing materials for the Waste Confidence proceedings, Dec. 21; many summary documents, notes and tables which describe various legislative proposals; materials generated by the Nuclear Assurance Corp.; Waste Confidence proceedings, Jan. 8 (Box 269., Folder 1-8)
        - 1982 Jan. 11-April. Includes material relating to the proposed Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1982 (Box 270., Folder 1-9)
        - 1982 May-June 15 (Box 271., Folder 1-7)
          - General
          - Hearings. Primarily Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, June 8 and 10
        - 1982 June 17-Sept. Udall Committee hearings, June 17 (Box 272., Folder 1-8)
        - 1982 Sept.-Nov. Versions of H.R. 7187 and H.R. 3809 (version eventually passed); draft versions of Commission Waste Confidence Decision (Box 273., Folder 1-10)
        - 1982 Dec.-1983 Feb. Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1982 passed, Dec. 20; additional drafts of Waste Confidence Decision (Box 274., Folder 1-10)
        - 1983 March-July. Relates to Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1982. Church/Domenici Committee hearings, May 2, Udall Committee hearings, May 26; additional drafts of Waste Confidence Decision (Box 275., Folder 1-10)
        - 1983 Sept.-1984 March. Additional Waste Confidence Decision drafts and a DOE report on the proceedings of a waste management meeting (Box 276., Folder 1-7)
      - Reprocessing. SEE ALSO: INTERNATIONAL REGULATION AND EXPORT LICENSING/General/General (non-proliferation and plutonium)
        - General, 1975-1983. Includes a report by Oak Ridge Laboratory, "Simple Quick Processing Plant," a related NRC review report and an inquiry from Senator Glenn, 1977 Aug.-1978 Jan. (Box 277., Folder 1-8)
        - CIVEX. Reports, correspondence and memoranda relating to an alternative reprocessing method developed by EPRI, 1978 (Folder 9-11)
        - GEMSO (Generic Environmental Impact Statement on Mixed Oxide Fuel), 1980 May-1981 Nov. (Box 278., Folder 1)
      - Security. SEE: NUCLEAR REACTOR SAFETY AND RESEARCH/Security/Fuel
      - Storage
        - General
          - General. Temporary storage, 1977 Sept.-1983 April (Folder 2-6)
          - Sheffield disposal site (Folder 7-8)
            - 1977 Dec.-1979 March
            - 1979 April-Aug. (Box 279., Folder 1-2)
          - West Valley disposal site, 1981 Sept.-1982 June (Folder 3-4)
        - Geologic repositories
          - 1980 April-Dec. NRC report on licensing procedures (Folder 5-9)
          - 1981 Jan.-June. Licensing procedures (Box 280., Folder 1-11)
          - 1981 June-1984 Jan. Briefing material for a meeting relating to DOE siting guidelines (Box 281., Folder 1-10)
          - 1984 March-June. Background materials (?) for a trip to Palo Verde, Arizona (Box 282., Folder 1-5)
      - Transportation, 1980 Oct.-1982 Oct. (Folder 6)
  - Personnel
    - Management
      - General. Relates to requirements for senior managers and financial qualifications review, 1983 May-1984 March (Folder 7-8)
      - Institute of Nuclear Power Operations (INPO)
        - 1980-1984 Jan. Largely workshop materials and materials evidently collected in response to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request (Box 283., Folder 1-9)
        - 1984 Jan. FOIA request (contd.) (Box 284., Folder 1)
    - Navy procedures, 1979 July-1980 Feb. (Folder 2)
    - Operator training and licensing
      - 1974 Feb.-1979 May. Includes a report contracted by the NRC from the Engineering Research Institute, Nuclear Safety Research Group (University of Iowa), entitled, "Evaluation of Gross Operator Error Rates Based on Past Experiences in Commerical Nuclear Reactors," 1978 Oct; also includes a testimony transcript with cover letter from Admiral Hyman Rickover 1980 Jan.-Nov. Includes operator exams, ca. 1979 May (Folder 3-8)
      - 1979 June-1981 June. Gilinsky drafts of proposed rule for operator qualifications, 1981 May (Box 285., Folder 1-8)
      - 1981 June-1982 June. Includes a report by General Physics Corp., "Program Plan: Task Analysis of Nuclear Power Plant Control Room Crews", with cover memorandum, 1982 June (Box 286., Folder 1-9)
      - 1982 July-1984 March. Includes OIA report, "Review of Reactor Operator Licensing," 1983 April, and a NRC report on drug and alcohol abuse, (NUREG/CR-3196), 1983 July (Box 287., Folder 1-7)
      - 1984 March-June. Includes material concerning policymaking for senior managers and reactor operator examinations (Box 288., Folder 1-8)
    - Security. Access authorization ("Insider Rule") and substance abuse problems, 1983 Jan.-1984 June. SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR SAFETY AND RESEARCH/Security (Box 289., Folder 1-3)
  - Siting
    - General
      - General
        - 1978 Oct.-1979 Nov. (Folder 4-8)
        - 1980 Jan.-1984 June (Box 290., Folder 1-6)
      - Sandia Labs. Report entitled, "Technical Criteria for Siting Criteria Development"
        - Draft, 1982 April (Folder 7-9)
        - Final, 1982 July (Box 291., Folder 1-2)
        - Related material. Includes two reports by David Strip, "Estimates of the Financial Consequences of a Nuclear Power Reactor Accident" and "Analysis of a Proposed One Thousand Dollar per Man-REM Cost Effectiveness Criterion," ca. 1982 Sept.-Oct.; NRC press conference, 1982 Nov. 1; material relating to a trip to Sandia Labs by Dr. Gilinsky, 1984 Jan.-Feb. (Folder 3-5)
    - Offshore sites (floating nuclear power stations)
      - 1975 May (Folder 6)
      - 1978 Oct.-Nov. (Folder 7-8)
      - 1978 Nov.-1982 June (Box 292., Folder 1-8)
      - 1982 Aug.-1983 March (Box 293., Folder 1)
    - Seismic issues
      - General
        - General. Includes reports about earthquake damage prediction and safety assessment
          - 1976 May-1982 Nov. (Folder 2-4)
          - 1982 June-Nov. (Folder 5)
        - Union of Concerned Scientists petition, 1979 March-1980 March
      - Large-scale shut-down, 1979 Feb. 13. Operations at five reactors were suspended because it was discovered that the computer codes used to calculate stresses on piping were in error
        - General
          - 1976 June-Oct. (Folder 6)
          - 1979 March 13-19. Hart Committee hearings, March 16 (Folder 7-9)
          - 1979 March-Oct. Udall Committee hearings, March 19 (Box 294., Folder 1-4)
        - Beaver Valley, 1979 March-Aug. (Folder 5)
        - Fitzpatrick, 1979 March-Aug. (Folder 6)
        - Maine Yankee, 1979 March-July (Folder 7)
        - Surry (1 & 2), 1979 March-Aug. (Folder 8)
- NUCLEAR REACTOR SAFETY AND RESEARCH, 1957-1984
  - Agreement States Program. Relates to states' participation in regulatory procedures, radiation safety and fuel cycle programs
    - General. Relates to Udall Committee hearings, 1979 July 19
      - General. Notebook (Box 295., Folder 1-3)
      - Testimony
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Commissioner Gilinsky. Drafts and comments (Folder 5)
    - 1979 July-1982 July (Folder 6-9)
  - Emergency planning and procedures
    - General
      - 1974-1975 (Box 296., Folder 1)
      - 1977 (Folder 2)
      - 1978 July-1979 May. National emergency exercise held 1979 May 30-31 (Folder 3-11)
      - 1979 May-July (Box 297., Folder 1-11)
      - 1979 Aug.-Nov. Hearings of the Moffett Committee, 1979 Nov. 1 (Box 298., Folder 1-11)
      - 1979 Dec.-1980 June (Box 299., Folder 1-9)
      - 1980 June-1981 March. Includes a staff report on finalization of emergency planning rule, June 3 (Box 300., Folder 1-9)
      - 1981 April-Dec. (Box 301., Folder 1-10)
      - 1981 Dec.-1982 July (Box 302., Folder 1-10)
      - 1982 July-Dec. (Box 303., Folder 1-10)
      - 1983 Jan.-July. Hart/Simpson Committee hearings, April 15; Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, July 8 (Box 304., Folder 1-9)
      - 1983 Aug.-1984 April. Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, Aug. 2 (Box 305., Folder 1-11)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA)
      - General, 1979 Oct.-1981 March. Includes a report entitled, "State Radiological Emergency Planning and Preparedness in Support of Commercial Nuclear Power Plants" (Box 306., Folder 1-4)
      - Emergency Mobilization Preparedness Board. Action Plan (second draft), 1982 Dec. (Folder 5)
    - Incident Response Plan
      - General
        - 1980 Jan.-1982 Jan. (Folder 6-8)
        - 1982 March-1983 Feb. (Box 307., Folder 1-3)
      - Emergency Operations Facility (EOF), 1979 Oct.-1983 Aug. (Folder 4-5)
    - Information and communication systems
      - General
        - General. Reports to Congress, 1980 Sept. (Folder 6)
        - Accident Briefing Book, 1982 Dec. Collection of light-water reactor diagrams to be used in explaining problems to the public (Folder 7-8)
      - Emergency Notification System (ENS). Communication system, includes AT&T proposal, 1979 April-1980 July (Box 308., Folder 1-2)
      - Nuclear Data Link. Proposal by Sandia Labs, 1980 April (Folder 3-6)
      - Nuclear Safety Analysis Center. EPRI proposal, 1980 June (Folder 7)
  - Health and environmental issues. SEE ALSO: NRC TMI INVESTIGATIONS/Radiation effects
    - General. Includes reports comparing the relative safety of nuclear and other energy sources
      - 1975 April-1977 Feb. (Folder 8-9)
      - 1977 March-1979 Nov. (Box 309., Folder 1-5)
    - Environment. Relates to the Clean Air Act of 1977, indoor radon, and environmental quality policy-making, 1976 Sept.-1984 Jan. (Folder 6-10)
    - Occupational exposure
      - 1978 May-1980 Feb. (Folder 11-12)
      - 1980 March-1983 June (Box 310., Folder 1-9)
  - Research and policy development
    - General (Box 311., Folder 1-12)
      - 1964 Feb.-1982 May. Includes an NRC report, "Standard Format and Content of Safety Analysis Reports for Nuclear Power Plants," 1978 Nov.; information on Lawrence Livermore Laboratory, 1982 May
      - 1982 May-1983 Sept. Hearing of the House Committee on Science and Technology, Subcommittee on Energy Research and Production (Marilyn L. Bouquard, Chairman), 1982 June 15 (Box 312., Folder 1-3)
    - Accident liability. Price Anderson Act, 1975 Aug.-1983 June (Folder 4-6)
    - Generic Requirements
      - General
        - 1978 Dec.-1982 Feb. (Folder 7-10)
        - 1982 Feb.-Dec. (Box 313., Folder 1-4)
      - Committee to Review Generic Requirements. Meetings
        - 1981 Nov.-1982 Dec. (Folder 5-9)
        - 1983 Feb.-1984 Jan. (Box 314., Folder 1-2)
    - Risk Assessment
      - General
        - General. Reports. SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION/Siting/General/Sandia Labs
          - 1957 March. "Theoretical Possibilities and Consequences of Major Accidents in Large Nuclear Power Plants" (WASH-740) (Folder 3)
          - 1975 Oct. "Reactor Safety Study: An Assessment of Accident Risks in U.S. Commercial Nuclear Power Plants" (WASH-1400) (Rasmussen Report) (Folder 4-5)
          - 1978 Sept. "Risk Assessment Review Group Report to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission" (NUREG/CR-0400) (Lewis Report) (Folder 6)
          - 1979 April. National Academy of Sciences, "Risks Associated with Nuclear Power: A Critical Review of the Literature" (Folder 7)
        - 1972 Aug.-1976 Sept. (Folder 8)
        - 1976 Oct.-1978 Oct. Lewis report to Congressman Udall, 1978 Sept. (Box 315., Folder 1-12)
        - 1978 Nov.-1979 Feb. Development of NRC statement on Lewis report, with media reports (Box 316., Folder 1-12)
      - 1979 Feb.-1982 Jan. Udall Committee hearing, 1979 Feb. 26; comments on Lewis report; also includes material relating to radiation releases during reactor accidents, 1981 July-Oct. (Box 317., Folder 1-10)
    - Safety classification. Relates to the distinction between "important-to-safety" and "safety-related" factors, 1983 Nov.-1984 June (Box 318., Folder 1-5)
    - Safety Goals policy
      - 1980 Oct.-1982 June (Folder 6-10)
      - 1982 June-1983 Jan. Includes EPRI report, 1982 Dec. (Box 319., Folder 1-10)
      - 1983 Jan.-July (Box 320., Folder 1-5)
    - Severe Accident Research Plan (SARP). Includes industry reports relating to a core meltdown accident scenario
      - 1981 Nov.-1982 Aug. (Folder 6-9)
      - 1982 Aug.-1983 July (Box 321., Folder 1-7)
    - Systematic Evaluation Program (SEP). Relates to a program of reassessment of older reactors, 1979 Dec.-1983 March. Includes Udall hearing, 1981 Feb. 27 (Folder 8-10)
  - Specific real or potential problems
    - General
      - General, 1975 April-1984 Feb. (Box 322., Folder 1)
      - High temperature gas reactors (HTGR), 1978 Dec.-1984 Feb. (Folder 2-3)
    - Anticipated Transient without Scram (ATWS)
      - 1980 Sept.-1983 Aug. (Folder 4-7)
      - 1983 Sept.-1984 June (Box 323., Folder 1-4)
    - Cladding, 1980 Oct.-Nov. (Folder 5)
    - Containment. Relates to controversy surrounding pressure containment systems
      - 1972 Sept.-1980 Aug. (Folder 6-11)
      - 1981 Jan.-1982 July (Box 324., Folder 1-2)
    - Control systems. Relates to safety implications of potential failures, 1976 Dec.-1981 May (Folder 3)
    - Core cooling and degradation. Includes material on loss-of-fluid transients (LOFT)
      - 1976 April-1979 Sept. (Folder 4-9)
      - 1979 Oct.-1981 March (Box 325., Folder 1-5)
    - Electrical safeguards (includes fire protection). Equipment Qualification Rule relating to environmental qualification of electrical components
      - 1977 June-1980 Feb. (Folder 6-13)
      - 1980 March-Nov. (Box 326., Folder 1-11)
      - 1981 Jan.-1982 May (Box 327., Folder 1-9)
      - 1982 June-1983 April (Box 328., Folder 1-10)
      - 1984 March-June (Box 329., Folder 1-3)
    - Hydrogen control. Relates primarily to the explosive resistance of ice containment systems such as those at Sequoyah and D.C. Cook nuclear power plants
      - 1980 Feb.-Aug. (Folder 4-12)
      - 1980 Sept.-1983 June. Includes report by Bechtel Power Corp. relating to the Pilgrim 2 plant, "Evaluation of Hydrogen Combustibility and Control under Degraded Core Conditions," 1980 Dec. 3 (Box 330., Folder 1-9)
    - Piping systems, 1975 Feb.-1984 March. Primarily relates to intergranular stress corrosion cracking (IGSCC); five reactors shut down, 1983 July 14
      - 1975 Feb.-1983 Nov. (Box 331., Folder 1-9)
      - 1983 Dec.-1984 March (Box 332., Folder 1)
    - Pressurized Thermal Shock (PTS)
      - 1980 May-1982 May. Includes undated notes, outline and a typescript report (Folder 2-11)
      - 1982 May-1983 July (Box 333., Folder 1-5)
    - Steam generators. Tube ruptures and turbine cracks, 1980 Feb.-1983 March (Folder 6)
    - Relief and safety valves. Includes power-operated relief valves (PORV), implicated in the TMI-2 accident
      - 1981 March-1983 April (Folder 7-8)
      - 1983 April-1984 April (Box 334., Folder 1-4)
  - Security
    - Fuel
      - General, 1978 March-April. Relates to an offer of sale to Westinghouse of uranium-235 and a subsequent FBI investigation (Folder 5)
      - ERDA-NRC Task Force. Formed 1976 March, to develop safeguards at nuclear fuel cycle facilities processing strategic quantities of weapons-usable special nuclear materials (SSNM)
        - 1976 Jan.-Aug. (Folder 6-10)
        - 1976 Sept.-Dec. Task force report, Nov. 23 (Box 335., Folder 1-9)
        - 1976 Dec.-1977 Jan. (Box 336., Folder 1-2)
      - Integrated Safeguard Information System (ISIS), Relates to a proposal for a system for material accounting, 1982 March-1983 June (Folder 3-10)
      - Materials-Unaccounted-for (MUF). Relates to inventories of SSNM, 1974 Dec.-1982 July (Box 337., Folder 1-4)
      - Safeguards Upgrade Rule. Task Force on NRC Safeguards Policy established, 1979 Jan. 26 (Folder 5-7)
        - 1977 Dec.-1978 April
        - 1978 April-1979 June (Box 338., Folder 1-6)
    - Terrorism and sabotage
      - General, 1971 Sept.-1984 Jan. (Folder 7-8)
      - Glenn/Percy Committee hearings, and subsequent anti-terrorism legislation (H.R. 13225, H.R. 13283, S. 2236)
        - 1978 Jan. (Folder 9)
        - 1978 Jan.-1979 March. Gilinsky testimony, March 23 (Box 339., Folder 1-10)
- REACTOR SITES, 1974-1984
  - General
    - General. Primarily relates to the proposed conversion from the use of high-enriched uranium to low-enriched uranium fuel in research reactors
      - General, 1977 Sept.-1984 June (Box 340., Folder 1-3)
      - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), 1982 March-1984 Jan. (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1981 Feb.-1984 June. Includes academics, industry and government officials, and U.S. Congress (Folder 5-10)
    - Meeting materials. Transcripts, reports, notes and letters
      - 1983 Dec. 19 (Box 341., Folder 1-2)
      - 1984 Jan. 27 (Folder 3-4)
    - Reports
      - 1980 Aug. IAEA, "Research Reactor Core Conversion from the Use of Highly Enriched Uranium to the Use of Low Enriched Uranium Fuels Guidebook" (Folder 5)
      - 1983 Sept. "Converting Reactors at Academic Institutions from HEU to LEU". Prepared by Gerald Pollack for Dr. Gilinsky. Includes memoranda, letters, notes, charts, other miscellany (Folder 6-7)
      - 1983 Nov. LEU (Low Enrichment Uranium) Study Group report. Draft and final copy (Box 342., Folder 1-2)
  - Bailly (Indiana)
    - General. Notebook, 1977-1979 (Folder 3-8)
    - 1974-1982. Construction cancelled, 1981 Aug. (Box 343., Folder 1-7)
  - Big Rock Point (Michigan)
    - 1980-1981. Relates to spent fuel pool storage expansion (Folder 8-9)
    - 1982-1983. Relates to spent fuel pool storage and emergency procedures (Box 344., Folder 1-2)
  - Browns Ferry (Alabama)
    - 1975 March-1982 May. Includes material relating to the 1975 fire and subsequent fire protection violations (Folder 3-12)
    - 1982 May-1984 Feb. Relates to low level waste storage, and a transient event, 1984 Feb. 14 (Box 345., Folder 1-2)
  - Brunswick (North Carolina). Relates to investigation and enforcement action
    - General. Notebook, 1980 Sept.-1982 Nov. (Folder 3)
    - 1982 April-1983 March (Folder 4-10)
    - 1983 May and Nov. (Box 346., Folder 1)
  - Byron (Illinois)
    - 1981 June-1984 Jan. Atomic Safety and Licensing Board (ASLB) denial of operating license due to quality assurance deficiencies, 1984 Jan. 13 (Folder 2-7)
    - 1984 Feb.-April. Inspection report, 1984 Feb. (Box 347., Folder 1-3)
  - Callaway (Missouri), 1984 May (Folder 4)
  - Catawba (North Carolina)
    - 1982 Dec.-1983 Nov. Site visit, 1983 Sept. (Folder 5-9)
    - 1983 Nov.-1984 May. TDI generator problems, 1984 Feb.; review of NRC handling of allegations, 1984 May (Box 348., Folder 1-4)
  - Clinch River (Tennessee)
    - General. Notebook, 1976 Aug.-Nov. (Folder 5-7)
    - General. Notebook (contd.) (Box 349., Folder 1-5)
    - 1976 July-1977 Feb. Environmental report (NUREG 0139), 1977 Feb. (Folder 6-8)
    - 1977 July-1981 Dec. Hart/Simpson Committee hearing, 1977 July 11; Dingell Committee hearing, 1981 July 21 (Box 350., Folder 1-9)
    - 1981 Dec. Primarily reports to support DOE exemption request to begin site preparation, 1981 Dec. (Box 351., Folder 1-9)
    - 1981 Dec.-1982 Jan. DOE reports and submissions from other interested parties (Box 352., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 Feb-June. Request denied, March (Box 353., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 July 1-28. Second DOE exemption request submitted; NRC environmental report (draft of NUREG 0139, Supplement 1) (Box 354., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 July 29-Aug. Consideration of second DOE exemption request (Box 355., Folder 1-8)
    - 1982 Aug.-Nov. Investigation of allegations; NRC environmental reports (NUREG 0139, Supplement 1, Vols. 1-2); second DOE request granted Aug. 17 (Box 356., Folder 1-7)
    - 1982 Dec.-1983 April. Limited Work Authorization decision, 1983 Feb. (Box 357., Folder 1-10)
    - 1983 May-1984 March. NRC safety report, 1983 May; Congress declines to continue funding, 1983 Oct.; Los Alamos report on accident potential, 1984 March (Box 358., Folder 1-4)
  - Comanche Peak (Texas). Relates to intra-agency controversy over investigations of the facility
    - 1982 Aug.-1983 Oct. (Folder 5-8)
    - 1983 Oct.-1984 March (Box 359., Folder 1-2)
  - Cooper (Nebraska), 1982 Jan.-1983 Feb. Investigation and enforcement action (Folder 3-9)
  - Crystal River (Florida), 1979 May-1980 March. Transient event, 1980 Feb. 26. SEE ALSO: NRC TMI Investigations/ Babcock & Wilcox/Reports
    - 1979 May-1980 March (Folder 10-12)
    - 1980 March-1983 March (Box 360., Folder 1-2)
  - D.C. Cook (Michigan), 1981 Sept.-1984 April. Investigations (NRC and the Department of Justice), NRC investigation report, 1983 Feb. (Folder 3-7)
  - Davis Besse (Ohio), 1983 Oct.-1984 March. Transient event, 1984 March 2. SEE ALSO: NRC TMI INVESTIGATIONS/Babcock & Wilcox/General (Folder 8)
  - Diablo Canyon (California). Relates to seismic problems, construction reevaluation and safety studies. Reports, briefs, transcripts, correspondence, memoranda, clippings
    - 1978 Nov. Pacific Gas and Electric Company-sponsored (PG&E) report, "Seismic Evaluation for Postulated 7.5 M Hosgri Earthquake" (Folder 9-11)
    - 1978 Nov. Pacific Gas and Electric Company-sponsored (PG&E) report, "Seismic Evaluation for Postulated 7.5 M Hosgri Earthquake" (contd.) (Box 361., Folder 1-8)
    - 1978 Nov. Pacific Gas and Electric Company-sponsored (PG&E) report, "Seismic Evaluation for Postulated 7.5 M Hosgri Earthquake" (contd.) (Box 362., Folder 1-9)
    - 1979 Dec.-1981 Feb. Notebook relating to approval for fuel loading and low power testing (Box 363., Folder 1-8)
    - 1981 March-Aug. Atomic Safety and Licensing Review Appeal Board endorsement of seismic design specifications (ALAB-644), June 16; site visit, July 10; low power testing approved, July 17 (Box 364., Folder 1-11)
    - 1981 Aug.-Sept. PG&E notifies NRC of potential problems in the seismic analysis of systems and equipment, Sept. 28 (includes extensive reports on technical specifications) (Box 365., Folder 1-9)
    - 1981 Sept. Includes reports on technical specifications (Box 366., Folder 1-8)